

CONTACT ME AT



flyindessert@gmail.com



+ 32 4999915516



https://www.linkedin.com/in/manojfernando-web-developer/

TECHNICAL SKILLS

















Bootstrap

Vue

ExpressJs

SQL







Node.js

NoSQL

SOFT SKILLS

Team-player

Problem-Solver

Quick Learner

Active Listener

Passion & Curiosity

LANUAGES

Sinhala - Native Lanuage

English - Excellent

Dutch- A2 proficiency

AWARDS RECEIVED

- Top 10 Campaigns on Google AdWords ,Udacity (2018)
- Student of the Month,
 OpenClassrooms (2021)

INTERESTS

Travel

Environment

Reading

Crypto Enthusiast

MANOJ FERNANDO

WEB DEVELOPER & DIGITAL MARKETER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Highly self-motivated with never give up attitude professional committed to pursuing a long-term career change in Web Development. 10 years of experience in a fast-moving retail sales environment and Plastic Injection Molding environment.

Eagerly waiting to join you as a team player with excellent communication skills and a passion for problem solving.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Diploma Web Development - OpenClassrooms

Online training course | 2019- 2021

- Integrate a mobile website with animations in CSS
- Optimize an Existing Website
- Build an e-commerce Website with JavaScript
- Build a Secure API for a Review App
- Build a Full-Stack Solution (MEVN Stack)

Digital Marketing Nanodegree Program - Udacity

Online training course | 2018

- Social Media Marketing
- Evaluate a Facebook Campaign
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO) Audit
- Evaluate a Google Ads Campaign
- Market with Email

Business Administration, Management and Operations

OpenArc School Of Business and Technology

Sri Lanaka | 2018

WORK EXPERIENCE

Machine operator

DS Smith | Belgium (2016-present)

Freelance Social Media Marketer

Belgium (2016-present)

Executive

Arpico | Sri Lanka (2015)

Department Supervisor & Purchase

Ansar Group | Qatar (2012-2014)